<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Cerulean</title>
    <link>http://xugr.me/GoMDL/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Cerulean</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://xugr.me/GoMDL/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate from Jekyll</title>
      <link>http://xugr.me/GoMDL/post/2015/03/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xugr.me/GoMDL/post/2015/03/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png  should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png  Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>http://xugr.me/GoMDL/post/2014/09/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xugr.me/GoMDL/post/2014/09/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>http://xugr.me/GoMDL/post/2014/04/hugo-template-primer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xugr.me/GoMDL/post/2014/04/hugo-template-primer/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>http://xugr.me/GoMDL/post/2014/04/getting-started-with-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xugr.me/GoMDL/post/2014/04/getting-started-with-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Goto hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your os and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at installing hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
 Clone the hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313  Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://xugr.me/GoMDL/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xugr.me/GoMDL/about/</guid>
      <description> Ray Xu 17 岁零 1040 多天。
理想是深刻认识信息。
喜欢  基础学科 理性讨论各种奇妙话题 颜色 Cerulean(#007BA7)，可能改变 哈利·波特和理性之道  游戏  轻度游戏玩家 Minecraft International VVVVVV  电子设备  ThinkPad OnePlus 3T Kindle iPad mini  语言  草草写过  Python Matlab C/C++ TeX  写过一点儿  Javascript Shell  Hello World  Ruby PHP   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>http://xugr.me/GoMDL/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xugr.me/GoMDL/resume/</guid>
      <description>Profile An undergraduate in Zhejiang University.
Majored in information engineering.
Managed several design projects(including web applications, websites, and Android project).
Experience  Designer, in Chu Kochen Student Union. UI Design Director and Web developer, in QSC Team. UI Designer and Product Manager, in Houaa. Ops for a simple web server, in Danqing Community, Qiushi College, Zhejiang University.  Education  College of Information Science &amp;amp; Electronic Engineering, Zhejiang Unversity Gaoxin No.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>